thailand-property.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Thailand-Property

At thailand-property.com, we take your online security very seriously, and we're committed to protecting your privacy and personal information. We've compiled this statement to explain how we collect, use, and secure your information. Please read on, and visit our Terms of Use for more information.

## Information We Collect & How We Use It

The thailand-property.com website requests and collects personal information from our customers at various site locations and instances, including, but not limited to, when you create a thailand-property.com membership, make a purchase, communicate with us via social media, write a product review, create a shortlist, participate in events, contests, or promotions, contact our customer care team, or post other customer-generated content to this Site. These are currently the primary ways in which we gather information, however, we may also collect data through other channels in the future.

The types of personal information we may collect from you can vary according to the method through which it was attained. It may include, but is not limited to, the following:

**a) Information You Provide to Us**

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us, such as:

  * Full name
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Billing information and payment details (such as billing address, credit card details, and other sensitive financial information, specifically for the purpose of completing your transaction)
  * Username and password for your thailand-property.com membership
  * A record of your thailand-property.com orders, purchase history.
  * Information provided by you through your interactions with us in social media
  * Location and geographic information that could be collected if you use our mobile site or app.
  * Other details that you may submit to us or may be included in the information provided to us by third parties
  * Additionally, when you select to email a friend about thailand-property.com, we request their email address from you to send them a one-time email. We do not share your friend's email information for any other purposes unless that friend creates a membership to thailand-property.com

**b) Information Collected Automatically**

We use third-party website analytics tools (including Google Analytics) that automatically collect non-personally identifiable information from your browser to our server logs whenever you interact with our Site. Such information includes, but is not limited to, IP address, pages viewed, site navigation patterns, details about the devices used to access the Internet and our Site, and geo-location tracking information if you are accessing our Site from a mobile device. It is obtained by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons. "Cookies" are text files that are transferred to your computer's hard drive as you navigate our Site and other sites. We use cookies to help us show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction and to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services, site experiences, and tools in the future. You may be able to adjust the preferences on your browser or device to change your device's acceptance of cookies, but doing so may limit our ability to provide content tailored to you.

We may collect and store non-personally identifiable usage information (including frequency and number of visitors to our Site). Such data is used only in aggregate form and in a manner that assures your anonymity. We may provide this anonymous, aggregate information to our partners and our partners may additionally use such information in order to determine general usage patterns and trends in an effort to provide you with an improved online experience.

**c) Email & Other Communications**

We may contact you via email to send you necessary related messages.

We may also send you newsletters and additional email messages about our products, services, contests, and promotions that we feel may be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive these and other promotional communications from us, you may select the unsubscribe link which is present in each email. You may also customize your communication preferences by accessing the email preference center in your thailand-property.com Membership Page and adjusting your settings accordingly.

## How We Use Your Information

All of the personal information we collect from our customers is for the purpose of the reasoning described above (see sections b & c), as well as:

  * Processing, verifying, validating, and completing your transaction
  * Creating, managing, and maintaining your membership to this Site
  * Providing requested live customer support and services
  * Record keeping of your purchase history
  * Enabling communication via our Site, blog, and social networks
  * Managing your participation in contests and promotions
  * Sending email as appropriate (See Section c: Email & Other Communications)

## Under 16?

thailand-property.com is intended for users who are 16 years of age and older. If you are under the age of 16, you are not permitted to submit any personal information to thailand-property.com. We will promptly delete any personal information from a person under the age of 16 should we discover that we have collected such information from a person under the age of 16 without verification of parental consent. If you believe we may have collected information from a person under the age of 16, please promptly contact info@dotpropertygroup.com so we can correct.

## Information Sharing

thailand-property.com does not share the personal information of its users with any unaffiliated third parties for their promotional purposes. We share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties only as described below:

## Payment, Shipping, Referral, & Other Programs

We might choose to use a third party payment processor and a third party shipping agent to ensure the payment and or any delivery required…. We also use a third party to administer our referral program. We may use other third parties for other services from time to time. These third parties have no authority to use your personal information for their own promotional purposes.

## Legal Disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose personal information to our service providers, the government, law enforcement agencies, or other third parties under certain circumstances where a formal request has been made (such as in responding to a court order, subpoena, or judicial proceeding) as thailand-property.com, in our sole and absolute discretion, deems necessary and appropriate. Moreover, in the event of a sale, merger, or transfer of some or all of thailand-property.com assets, or dissolution or bankruptcy, your personal information may be transferred to an unaffiliated third party as part of or apart from other transferred assets or assets. Any transfer will then be governed by and be the responsibility of any purchaser of or successor to the transferred assets or assets. We shall notify you by a notice on the home page of any change in the information practices governing your personal information as a result of any transfer of assets or any asset change in ownership, and your choices in how your information is used.

## Links to Third Party Websites

This Site contains links to other websites. thailand-property.com takes no responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of each website you visit prior to disclosing your personal information.

## User-Generated Content & Information Disclosure

Any personal information or image content you voluntarily disclose online in a manner that other users can view (including, but not limited to: reviews, comments, contributions to social media pages, in connection with contests and promotions, and on the thailand-property.com blog) becomes publicly available, and can be read, collected, and used by other members of this forum to send you unsolicited messages. Your membership name, email, or other information may also be displayed when you post comments or upload images throughout the Site. thailand-property.com is not responsible for the personal information users select to disclose in these forums.

## How We Protect Your Information

thailand-property.com utilizes some of the most advanced technology available today for Internet security purposes. When you access our checkout using industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, your information is protected with both server authentication and data encryption, ensuring that your data is safe, secure, and available only to thailand-property.com.

In addition, thailand-property.com is hosted in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or outside access to keep us all safe!

## Accessing Your Personal Information & Preferences

You can access, update, or change your personal information and communication preferences by signing into your thailand-property.com membership page and modifying your preferences at your discretion.   
You can choose not to provide us with any or all of the information we specify or request, but then you may not be able to create a membership with us or to take advantage of some or all of our features. 

## Your Privacy Rights

To obtain this information from thailand-property.com please send an email message to info@dotpropertygroup.com with "thailand-property.com Privacy Information" on the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your email address in response.

## Privacy Policy Updates

thailand-property.com may, at any time and without notice, modify and update this Privacy Policy by revising it on the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of any such revisions. You should therefore periodically visit this page to review the current Privacy Policy.   
***Last updated 19-Mai-2015 

## Contact Us

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about this Privacy Policy and Site.

You can reach us at: info@dotpropertygroup.com
